Nattell, Tom; Papers apap191
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Events, 1974-2002; Undated; 1; 7.3 cubic ft.
  - RAEW: reading pledges, income calculations, 1987 October 12; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 33)
  - RAEW press releases for 1998, 1992 events, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 34)
  - RAEW Programs 1989-1993, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 35)
  - RAEW: pledges, receipt, press release, income calculations, pledge tally, 1989 May 05-1990 December 22; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 36)
  - RAEW: Volunteers list and schedule for readings, 1989-1993; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 37)
  - RAEW: sponsor and donation list, phone prompts, income calculations, 1989; 1995 May 05; 1991 November 20 (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 38)
  - RAEW: pledge collection form letters, 1990 May 05; 1990 December 22 (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 39)
  - RAEW: galley proofs, press releases, 1992 May 01; 1993; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 40)
  - RAEW 1993: poster, press release, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 41)
  - Readings: Henson/Calhoun, Undated (Drawer E4, Video-tape 72)
  - RAEW: time sheets for readings, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 7)
  - "Rising from the Ashes" Hiroshima and Nagasaki days event: clippings, photographs, promotional materials, 1981 May 28-1988 August 09; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 42)
  - Rothenberg, Jerome: press release, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 43)
  - RONGS 88 editor track, Undated (Drawer E4, Video-tape 73)
  - Save Planet Earth International Mail Art Exhibit: scrapbook, Undated (Box 8 (1-Events), Folder 1)
  - Shots of Albany NC- 1300, Undated (Drawer E4, Video-tape 74)
  - Six Sundays at 3: correspondence, clippings, press release, 1990 June-1990 July 22; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 44)
  - SJC "Awards not Swords" dinner, 1988 October 30 (Drawer E4, Video-tape 75)
  - SJC tape - interview, Undated (Drawer E4, Video-tape 76)
  - SPC TV Jacobs dub w/ Father Bauer added, 1989 March 12 (Drawer E4, Video-tape 77)
  - Stone Rally, Golf Course, 1989 June 03; 1989 June 30 (Drawer E4, Video-tape 78)
  - Sun Day 1992: correspondence, supporter lists, statement of principles and goals, 1991 August 27; 1991 September 20; 1991 November 16; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 45)
  - Three guys from Albany: March/April 1994 performance schedule, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 46)
  - Tom's Trash: press release, 1995 April 01; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 47)
  - Universal declaration human rights, Undated (Drawer E4, Video-tape 79)
  - Untitled Cassette, Undated (Drawer E4, Video-tape 80)
  - Untitled Cassette, Undated (Drawer E4, Video-tape 81)
  - Untitled Cassette, 1987 (Drawer E4, Video-tape 82)
  - USS Albany Protest, 1987 June (Drawer E4, Video-tape 83)
  - USS Albany Protest: clippings, letterhead, press releases, correspondence, 1986 December 23-1990 July 02 (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 48)
  - Vega/Hanson: photographs, negatives, clippings, correspondence, 1986 January 26-1990 January 30; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 49)
  - Vend'art: correspondence, earth post 1993 poster, 1988 October 31; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 50)
  - Waldman, Anne with Michael Eck and Scott Smith at the QE2, 29:50, 1989 October 07 (Drawer E4, Video-tape 84)
  - Waldman, Anne QE2 performance, Writers Institute: correspondence, clippings, photographs, sponsor's report, 1989 January 24-1996 November 13; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 51)
  - Watervliet Arsenal, Undated (Drawer E4, Video-tape 85)
  - "Women for America, For the World" documentary showing: receipts, correspondence, clippings, 1987 July; 1987 September 01; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 52)
  - "Words in Situ" spoken word series: correspondence, clippings, photographs, posters, 1988 March-1988 July 6; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 53)
  - "Words in Situ" spoken word series: fliers, contract, correspondence, event calendar, 1988 December 31; 1989 January 03; 1989 July 01; Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 54)
  - Why the Death Penalty is Wrong: event flier, Undated (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 55)
  - Zaloom, Paul "Theater of Trash": photos, clippings, press releases, calendar, biography, 1982 January 16-1987 May 15 (Box 2 (1-Events), Folder 56)
- Biographical, 1956-1995; Undated; 2; 2.05 cubic ft.
  This series contains documents related to Nattell's personal, educational and occupational life. It contains a small number of poems by Nattell, photographs, correspondence, articles authored by Nattell, scholarly articles used during his education and newspaper clippings that are by, about, or mention him. Notable topics in this series include his research on the multiply-disabled and community support systems (CSS). Also included are Income Maintenance Training Evaluation forms and documents from the University at Albany's School of Social Welfare prepared by Nattell.
  - 12 Days of Christmas: list, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 1)
  - "A Day on the Ward", Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 2)
  - Activates of Daily Living (ADL) Study: article, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 3)
  - "Advocate" newsletter, 1979 October (Oversized 1, Folder 8)
  - Advocate groups: list of psychiatric inmates' organization: advocate newsletter, 1979 October; 1980 February 16; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 4)
  - Adult activity index: a pilot study of the community adjustment index, 1978 June (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 5)
  - "An Analysis of the Effects of Previous Social Work Experience on the Values of Beginning MSW students", 1977 November 23 (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 6)
  - Articles by Nattell: "Repatriation Study", "CARA Club: Policies and Procedures, Ideology and Integration in a Community Mental Health Organization", "The CARA Club: a Psycho-Social club", Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 7)
  - Articles by or about Nattell, 1979 April 30-1997 April 30; Undated (Box 1 (2-Biographical), Folder 9)
  - "Basic Principles of Art Therapy" article by Dee Carroll, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 8)
  - Birthday cards from Nattell's mother, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 9)
  - Budget requests for a study of housing in Albany's South End, 1995 November 17 (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 10)
  - "The Call for a Management Stance" article by Jerry S. Turem, 1974 September (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 11)
  - "The Capital District Psychiatric Club", 1976 October 06 (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 12)
  - CARA Club: notes, research materials, schedules, referral procedure", 1976 Fall-1980 August 5; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 13)
  - CARA Club: goals, news clippings, service group definition, 1979 January 30; 1979 March 26; 1979 Fall-1980 Winter; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 14)
  - "The Core Service Agency Concept: Implications for Future Planning and Legislation" by Judith E. Clark Turner and Cille Kennedy, 1979 August (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 15)
  - "Catij: A New Sociometric and its Application to a Prison Living Unity" article by Peter Killworth and H. Russell Bernard, 1974 Winter (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 16)
  - "Client Analysis and the Planning of Public Programs" article by Janet S. Reiner, Everett Reimer and Thomas A. Reiner, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 17)
  - Community articles and notes, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 18)
  - "Community Development Programs Serving the Urban Poor" by Charles F. Grosser, 1963 July (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 19)
  - "Community Health Evaluation Checklist - Lancaster House": evaluation, 1979 January 12 (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 20)
  - Community housing evaluation checklist, 1979 February; 1979 November (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 21)
  - Community mental health research articles, 1973; 1977 March; 1980 February; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 22)
  - "Community Resources and Protective Service Work in Child Welfare" by Steven I. Pflanczer, 1975 February-1975 May (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 23)
  - Community support system: case management approach in Alabama, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 24)
  - Community support system: documents and papers regarding minorities, 1979 November 05-1979 November 09 (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 25)
  - Community support system and community support project: documents, management plan, contract renewal, description of program, 1980-1981; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 26)
  - Community support system: evaluation forms, database printouts, 1979 February 15-1979 June 01; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 27)
  - Community support system and Office of Mental Health: quarterly report to the legislature, grant information, psychiatric center profile, adjustment index, 1978 July 01-1978 November 08; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 28-29)
  - Community support system: guidelines for year 3 progress report and year 4 program development plan, 1980 June; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 30)
  - Community support system: third year plan by Susan Steindorff, 1979 November 15 (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 31)
  - Community support project: third year progress report, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: assorted, 1981 November 14; 1982 April 26 (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 33)
  - Correspondence with officials regarding nuclear evacuation, 1983 March 16-1983 March 17; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 34)
  - Court documents: subpoena, deposition from police, traffic court document, 1985 November 13; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 35)
  - Cultural Influences on Mental Illness articles, 1977 November; 1978 November (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 36)
  - "Deinstitutionalization: A Cultural Perspective" paper by Nattell, one issue of Ripple newsletter, 1979 October; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 37)
  - "Deinstitutionalization: A Cultural Perspective" paper by Nattell, returned by American Psychological Association with letter, 1979 November 29 (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 38)
  - Department of Social Services Agency visit: reports, correspondence, 1980 February 14-1980 December 17; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 39)
  - Drug and Alcohol Articles, 1975-October 17 1978 (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 40-41)
  - Eight Step Coffeehouse: board minutes, financial reports, contracts, 1990 August 12-1992 February; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 42)
  - "Establishing a Computerized Management Information System" and "Hospitalization and Community Adjustment: a Study of Deinstitutionalized Patients" paper by Nattell, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 43)
  - "The Evolution of Community Residences: Same Outcome Measures" article by Richard Becker, 1980 February (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 44)
  - Evaluation Guidelines of a 314(d) project, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 45)
  - Evaluating a Model of a Community Support Services: notes, reports, 1978; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 46)
  - Exempt Post Evaluation: Ellis Hospital, telephone list, 1979 April 16; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 47)
  - "Family Functioning in the Low Income Black Community" article by Andrew Billingsley, 1986 December (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 48)
  - Fountain House: brochures, correspondence, handwritten notes, 1977 March; 1980 December (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 49)
  - "Friendship Networks: Their Formation and Functions in a Social Club for the Mentally Disabled" article by Nattell, correspondence edited drafts, receipts, 1972; 1980 September; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 50)
  - "The Fund of Sociability" drafts by Nattell, newsletter, draft of "Ethnology of a Social Club", 1980 September 16; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 51)
  - Grant writing, notes, program exercises, 1979 November 30-1980 January 28; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 52)
  - "Hiroshima," "The Columbus Fantasies: a New World Order" poems by Nattell, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 53)
  - "Hospitalization and Community Adjustment: A Study of Deinstitutionalizationalized Patients," staff views, and contacts with families of chronically mentally disabled adults, other articles by Nattell, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 54)
  - Housing and culture: notes, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 55)
  - "Impact of Social Work Education on Students' Values" article by Dorothy D. Hayes and Barbara K. Varley, 1965 July (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 56)
  - Imprisonment from the West Milton protest: correspondence, clippings, letters from individuals in jail, 1983 June 20-1983 July 24; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 57)
  - "In Defense of Social Work: An Examination of Stress in the Profession" article by Lydia Rappaport, 1960 March (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 58)
  - "Income Maintenance Training Institute: Evaluation Plan by Nattell, "Aspects of Poverty and Welfare" article by Timothy Murphy, Topic Ranking and Competency Expectations of Conference Participation" author unknown, 1981 May; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 59)
  - Income Maintenance Training Institute: evaluation forms, questionnaires, pre- and post-test forms, 1981 August; Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 60)
  - Income Maintenance Training Institute: evaluation forms, Undated (Box 3 (2-Biographical), Folder 61)
  - Income Maintenance Training Institute: memo, notes, correspondence, training manual, 1980 August 06; 1981 February 23; 1981 April 10; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 1)
  - Income Maintenance Training institute: session summary sheets, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 2)
  - Income Maintenance: topic ranking and competency expectations of conference participants, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 3)
  - Income Maintenance: notes, program outcome evaluations, memos, 1980 June 07-1981 June 02; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 4)
  - Level of Care survey, guidelines and codes, patient medication lists, 1978 December; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 5)
  - Mental Retardation or Developmental Disabilities: articles, 1967 November-1977 July (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 6)
  - Multiply-Disabled: correspondence, notes, computer code and data, policy draft and final New York law book on treatment of multiply-disabled individuals, 1978 March 17-1979 February 03; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 7)
  - Multiply-Disabled: correspondence, notes, questionnaires, definitions, research project program for the multiply-disabled, list of persons served in 1978 by mental hygiene programs, 1978 December 15-1979 April 06; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 8)
  - Multiply-Disabled: Report of the Task Force notes, computational code, survey for evaluating, Results tabulated in charts, 1978 October 01; 1979 January 01; 1980 May 06; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 9)
  - "National Plan for the Chronically Mentally Ill", Summary of the Mental health Systems Act, memo, notes, news clippings, Definitions for Guidelines and Guiding Principles for CSS, 1980 August 08; 1980 September 03; 1980 November 25 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 10)
  - "Networks and Places" article by Claude S. Fischer, notes, annotated printout, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 11)
  - New Alchemy Institute: 1980 calendar, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 12)
  - News clippings by or about Nattell, 1981 February 01-1994 April 17 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 13-14)
  - News clippings by or about Nattell, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 15)
  - Office of Mental Hygiene: documents and overviews, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 16)
  - "An Organizational Case Study: Secret Welfare Administration: article by Joseph Kaiser, 1977 November 29 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 17)
  - "Organizational Change as a Paradigm Shift" article by Allen Imeshein, 1978 April 05 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 18)
  - Photographs of Nattell at a toy safety demonstration, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 19)
  - Police Summons and bail receipt, 1983 November 23; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 20)
  - "Private Troubles and Public Issues: One Social Work Job or Two" article by William Schwartz, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 21)
  - "The Psychotic Subnormal" article by Rudolph Payne, 1978 November 14 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 22)
  - "Recent Federal Interagacy Initiatives and Pending Legislative Developments Related to Community Support Systems" by Paul J. Carling, 1979 October 29 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 23)
  - Repatriation Study: correspondence and drafts with, 1980 June 04; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 24)
  - "Repatriation Study: Where are the now?"article by Nattell and others, draft and other version, 1981 June 30; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 25)
  - Resumes by Nattell, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 26)
  - "Shamanism" paper by Nattell, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 27)
  - "A Study of Prevalence and Incidence Rates in Schenectady County"- author unknown, "The Emergency Room and the Psychiatric Client: Use or Misuse of Services" author unknown, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 28)
  - "A study of Prevalence and Incidence in Schenectady County"- author unknown, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 29)
  - Social interaction and mental health patients: articles, 1970 October; 1974 February; 1978; 1980 April 21 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 30)
  - Social Club Interview, Family Questionnaire- mental health, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 31)
  - "Social Networks and Pathways to Psychiatric Treatment" article by Allan Horwitz, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 32)
  - Social Welfare Models: syllabi from class, annotated bibliography, 1977 Fall; 1978 Fall; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 33)
  - "Sources of Stress - Among Student Practitioners in Social Work: A Sociological View" by John E. Mayer, Aaron Rosenblatt, 1974 Fall (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 34)
  - "Special Project Research Papers": articles, 1979 January; 1979 July; Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 35)
  - "Staff Burn-out: Diagnosis,Treatment, and Prevention" article by Werner M. Mendel, bibliography, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 36)
  - "Supervision in a Large Federal Agency: Psychiatric Setting" article by Eugene Cohen, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 37)
  - "Systematic Approach to Social Policy Analysis" article by David G. Gil, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 38)
  - "Task Force on Multi-Disabilities": research proposal, 1979 April 06 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 39)
  - Traffic court summons, 1985 November 06; 1985 December 05 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 40)
  - "Training Boards of Visitors of Mental Hygiene Facilities 1978-1979": report to the governor, 1980 January 24 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 41)
  - Uniform Client Data Instrument: client evaluation form, Undated (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 42)
  - "The Utility of System Models and Development Models for Practitioners" article by Robert Chin, "General Systems Theory - The Skeleton of Science" article by Kenneth Boulding, 1956 April; 1965 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 43)
  - "What are the needs of Chronic Mental Patients?" article by Robert Peterson, 1978 (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 44)
  - "When Children are afraid to start School" article by Benjamin Spock, 1975 August (Box 4 (2-Biographical), Folder 45)
- Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany Peace and Energy Council, 1979-1992; Undated; 3; 0.50 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  Nattell was a founding member of the political, economic and social activist groups CDANA/APEC. The group was originally called the Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance but at a meeting on January 18, 1982 changed the name to APEC to better reflect the organization's expanding areas of interest. This series contains many copies of the quarterly newsletter released by CDANA/APEC as well as the original publication galley proofs that were photocopied for the newsletter. Also included are newspaper clippings, article drafts, and galleys for tickets to events related to CDANA/APEC.
  - CDANA in the news, 1979 June 01; 1979 October 19; 1982 October (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 46)
  - APEC and CDANA: press releases, news clippings, 1979 October 09-1982 July 01 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 47)
  - CDANA/APEC: leaflets, events, letterhead, posters, 1979 November 12-1982 April 25; Undated (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 48)
  - CDANA/APEC: newsletters, galley proofs, 1980 December-1983 Winter (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 49)
  - CDANA/APEC: newsletters, galley proofs, 1982 Winter-1989 Winter (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 50-51)
  - APEC: newsletters, press releases, clippings, cartoons, galley proofs, support forms, 1982 January 23-1991 Spring (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 52)
  - News clippings and related material: folder for APEC, 1982 January 29-1987 October 7; Undated (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 53-54)
  - APEC: survey, article, drafts, news clippings, poem, 1982 August 29; 1982 February 28; Undated (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 55)
  - CDANA/APEC: galley proofs, tickets, CDANA letterhead, 1982 December; Undated (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 56)
  - APEC: newsletters, galley, 1982 Spring-1990 Summer (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 57)
  - APEC: civil defense council letters, galley, resolutions, 1983 January 19; Undated (Box 4 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 58)
  - APEC: news clippings, correspondence, press releases, 1983 December 10-1990 December 21; Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 1)
  - APEC: newsletters, galley proofs, 1985 Fall-1990 Winter; Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 2-3)
  - APEC: newsletters, 1988 Spring-1993 Winter; Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 4-5)
  - APEC: newsletters, galley proofs, correspondence regarding price chopper bags, bag, press releases, 1989 December 28-1993 Winter; Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 6)
  - APEC Seneca Army depot: press release, news clipping, 1990 March 28; 1990 May 24; 1990 June 15; Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 7)
  - APEC: correspondence with price chopper regarding light bulbs, 1991 August 01-1992 January 22; Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 8)
  - APEC: newsletters, galley proofs, 1992 Summer; Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 9)
  - APEC: alternatives directory, Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 10)
  - APEC: newsletter galley proofs, letterhead, news clipping, Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 11)
  - APEC: letterhead, galley, assorted press releases, Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 12)
  - APEC: galley proofs of art, Undated (Box 5 (3-Capital District Anti-Nuclear Alliance/Albany ), Folder 13)
- Subject Files for research, 1967-1998; Undated; 4; 2.25 cubic ft.